{
    "subject": "resource/Princesse_Tam-Tam",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "resource/French_language",
    "human_readable": "The language of Princesse Tam-Tam is French.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854393005371094,
            "question": "Is French the native language of Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9050389528274536,
            "question": "Would someone who speaks French understand Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8827987313270569,
            "question": "What language does Princesse Tam-Tam speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.826103150844574,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the language used in Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7720301151275635,
            "question": "In what language was Princesse Tam-Tam originally created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7699953317642212,
            "question": "Why is it important to know the language of Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7511515617370605,
            "question": "Are there any other languages that Princesse Tam-Tam might be translated into?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6040633916854858,
            "question": "How does the language used in Princesse Tam-Tam contribute to the story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15449802577495575,
            "question": "Is French a common language for children's stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05853293091058731,
            "question": "What are some other examples of children's stories that use French?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Princesse Tam-Tam is French.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1291_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is French a common language for children's stories?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1291_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the language used in Princesse Tam-Tam contribute to the story?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1291_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other languages that Princesse Tam-Tam might be translated into?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1291_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1291_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The language of Princesse Tam-Tam is French\" can be supported by the context information, which refers to the film as being part of a French film and cultural study. The documents mention that it is appropriate for \"bridge\" courses in French or are set in France, supporting the assertion that the language of the film is French."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}